The extraordinary and unfinished life of Anton Yelchin
Love, Antosha is a documentary film directed by Garret Price.
From a prolific career in film and television, Anton
Yelchin left an indelible legacy as an actor.
Through his journals and other writings, his photography, the original music he wrote, and interviews with his family, friends,
and colleagues, this film looks not just at Anton's impressive career, but at a broader portrait of the man.
Self (archive footage), played by Anton Yelchin.
Self, played by Viktor Yelchin.
Self, played by Irina Korina.
Narrator (voice), played by Nicolas Cage.
Self, played by Jennifer Lawrence.
Self, played by Chris Pine.
Love, Antosha is a 2019 American documentary film directed and produced by Garret
Price, focusing on the life and career of actor Anton Yelchin.
The film premiered in the Doc Premieres category at the 2019
Sundance Film Festival on January 28, 2019.
The film was released by Lurker Productions in New
York and Los Angeles in August 2019.